Guide to the Paul Davidson Papers, 1961-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, 1961-2004 and undated, (26 boxes)
  - Parkin, Michael, 1983-1992 (Box 17)
  - Parquez, Alain, 1983 and undated (Box 17)
  - Parrinello, Sergio, 1973-1996 (Box 18)
  - Pasinetti, Luigi, 1968-2000 (Box 18)
  - Patinkin, Don, 1968-1993 (Box 18)
  - Perelman, Michael, 1978-1989 (Box 18)
  - Perlman, Mark, 1977-1991 (Box 18)
  - Pesek, Boris, 1979-1985 (Box 18)
  - Peterson, Wallace, 1977-1992 (Box 18)
  - Pfaff, Martin, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Pheby, John, 1987-1994 (Box 18)
  - Pollin, Robert, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Pomer, Marshall, 1992-1995 (Box 18)
  - Pollock, Alex J., 1991 (Box 18)
  - Pope, William Henry, 1989-1993 (Box 18)
  - Posner, Michael, 1969-1979 (Box 18)
  - Post Keynesian Workshops, 1982-2000 (Box 18)
  - Poverty Institute (University of Wisconsin), 1986 (Box 18)
  - Powell, Alan, 1968-1974 (Box 18)
  - Powers, Trevil, 1988-1991 (Box 18)
  - Pressman, Steven, 1989-1996 (Box 18)
  - Public Broadcasting System, 1979 (Box 18)
  - The Public Interest, 1979-1981 (Box 18)
  - Public Interest Economics Center, 1973-1981 (Box 18)
  - Public Problems of the Domestic Crude Oil Industry, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
  - Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1969-1986 (Box 18)
  - Quarterly Review of Economics and Business, 1984 (Box 18)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1966-1993 (Box 18)
  - R Recent Miscellaneous, 1988-1998 (Box 18)
  - Radio talks, 1972-1978 (Box 18)
  - Ranson, R. David, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Rao, Vaman, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Rapping, Leonard, 1982-1986 (Box 18)
  - Recreation, outdoor: study, 1967-1977 (Box 18)
  - Reddaway, Brian, 1971-1976 (Box 18)
  - Rees, Albert, 1968-1991 (Box 18)
  - Reich, Robert, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Reprint Requests, 1968-1991 (Box 19)
  - Review of Economic Studies, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Reynolds, Peter, 1997-2000 (Box 19)
  - Riach, Peter, 1969-1993 (Box 19)
  - Rima, Ingrid, 1978-1988 (Box 19)
  - Roberts, David, 1978-1993 (Box 19)
  - Robinson, Austin, 1979-1987 (Box 19)
  - Robinson, Joan, 1967-1979, (5 folders) (Box 19)
  - Roll, Eric, 1979-1989 (Box 19)
  - Rotheim, Roy, 1974-1996 (Box 19)
  - Rousseas, Stephen, 1979-1991 (Box 19)
  - Routledge Publishing, 1990-1997 (Box 19)
  - Royal Economics Society, 1966-1988 (Box 19)
  - Runde, Jochen, undated (Box 20)
  - Russell, Milton, 1968-1993 (Box 20)
  - Rutgers Alumni Association, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Rutgers University, 1969-1989, (1-9 of 10 folders) (Box 20)
  - Rutgers University, 1969-1989, (10 of 10 folders) (Box 21)
  - Rutgers University Economics Department, 1975-1986, (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1969-1991 (Box 21)
  - S Unfiled, 1987-2000, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box 21)
  - S Unfiled, 1987-2000, (4 of 4 folders) (Box 22)
  - S'Agora conference, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Salant, Walter, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
  - Salvadori, Neri, 1989-1992 (Box 22)
  - Salvary, Stanley C., 1992 (Box 22)
  - Samuels, Warren, 1978-1992 (Box 22)
  - Samuelson, Paul A., 1967-1980 (Box 22)
  - Society for the Advancement of Socio-Economics (SASE), 1989-1993 (Box 22)
  - Sawyer, Malcolm, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Seidman, Lawrence, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
  - Sekiya, Kisaburo, 1979-1981 (Box 22)
  - Sen, Kunal, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
  - Seneca, Joseph, 1967-1986 (Box 22)
  - Shackle, G. L. S., 1972-1991 (Box 22)
  - Shapiro, Nina, 1980-1992 (Box 22)
  - Sharpe, M. E., 1978-1990, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Silk, Leonard (New York Times), 1977-1991 (Box 22)
  - Skidelsky, Robert, 1986-2002, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Smeeding, Timothy, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Smith, V. Kerry, 1971-1989 (Box 22)
  - Smithin, John, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Smolensky, Eugene, 1968-2003 (Box 23)
  - Social policy, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Social Science Encyclopedia, 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Solow, Robert, 1971-1985 (Box 23)
  - Southern Economics Association, 1967-1992 (Box 23)
  - Southern Economics Journal, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Speiser, Stuart, 1977-1992, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Steiger, Otto, 1978-1989 (Box 23)
  - Stein, Herbert, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Stiglitz, Joseph, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
  - Strasbourg University, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Summers, Lawrence, 1985-1988 (Box 23)
  - Suplicy, Eduardo, 1989-2002 (Box 23)
  - Sylos-Labini, Paolo, 1979-1991 (Box 23)
  - Szego, Andrea, 1985-1990 (Box 23)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1967-2004 (Box 23)
  - Taussig, Michael, 1995 (Box 23)
  - Teixeira, Joanilio R., 1990-1992 (Box 23)
  - Terzi, Andrea, 1982-1995 (Box 23)
  - Thirlwall, A. P., 1976-1999, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Thirlwall, A. P., 1976-1999, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Tijerina, Eliezer, 1976-1999 (Box 24)
  - Tobin, James, 1972-1995 (Box 24)
  - Torr, Christopher, 1977-1982 (Box 24)
  - Trevithick, James, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
  - Trieste Summer School, 1985-1987 (Box 24)
  - Trimmer-Smith, David, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Tsurumi, Hiroki, 1976-1980 (Box 24)
  - Tuggle, Francis D., 1980 (Box 24)
  - TV Script Channel 13 NYC, 1967 (Box 24)
  - Tyler, William G., 1975 (Box 24)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1976-1998 (Box 24)
  - University of Campinas (UNICAMP), Brazil, 1990 (Box 24)
  - United Nations, 1985-1997 (Box 24)
  - University of California-Santa Cruz, 1976-1978 (Box 24)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1974 (Box 24)
  - University of Kent (UK), 1974 (Box 24)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1962-1975 (Box 24)
  - University of Pennsylvania graduate students, 1968-1976 (Box 24)
  - University of Tennessee, 1984-1999, (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - University of Tennessee Economics Department, 1986-1988 (Box 24)
  - University of Texas - Austin, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
  - United States Department of Energy, 1978 (Box 24)
  - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1980-1999 (Box 24)
  - United Wrep Workers (UWW) Union, 1974 (Box 24)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1968-2000 (Box 25)
  - Vadakin, James C., 1980 (Box 25)
  - Van Dyke, Ted, 1981 (Box 25)
  - Vernon, Raymond, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Vickers, Douglas, 1973-1992 (Box 25)
  - Virgo, John M., 1974 (Box 25)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1964-2000, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Wallich, Henry C., 1977 (Box 25)
  - Wangro, Joseph, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Warsaw School of Economics, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Watanabe, Yoshio, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Weintraub, E. Roy, 1973-2004 (Box 25)
  - Weintraub, Neil, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Weintraub, Sidney, 1964-1983, (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Weitzman, Martin L., 1983 (Box 26)
  - Wells, Paul, 1967-1989 (Box 26)
  - Western Economics Association, 1973-1983 (Box 26)
  - Weymark, John A., 1975 (Box 26)
  - Wheeler, Kenneth, 1976-1980 (Box 26)
  - Who's Who in Economics, 1981-2000 (Box 26)
  - Who's Who, 1978-1980 (Box 26)
  - Wickens, Michael, 1970-1977 (Box 26)
  - Wijers, Hans, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Williams, Edward, 1978-1990 (Box 26)
  - Williamson, John, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Williamson, Oliver, 1983-1984 (Box 26)
  - Wold, Herman, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Woo, Henry, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Wray, L. Randall, 1989-1994 (Box 26)
  - Y and Z Miscellaneous, 1973-1989 (Box 26)
  - Zucker, Seymour (Business Week Magazine), 1969-1990 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous (letters without last names), 1972-1968 and undated (Box 26)
- Other Files Series, 1969-2000 and undated, (1 box)
  Consists of uncategorized files of drafts, newspaper clippings, reports, and other documents created through Davidson's professional activities. Arranged in alphabetical order by folder title.
  - Groningen University symposium proposal, undated (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous drafts, 1984 and undated (Box 26)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1969-1987 and undated (Box 26)
  - Referee report by Davidson, undated (Box 26)
  - S'Agora Spain conference proposal, undated (Box 26)
  - Various writings and interviews, 1972-2000 (Box 26)